(Dealer Plates)
Dealer Plates.
I just printed T.O.P.S. for the interstate
I just hit the auction, I'm biddin' lanes
Just hand me the AUX, I'll get you
paid. Dealer Plates. Dealer Plates.
I can vin-swap if you with the gang If
you with the cops, this for entertainment
Just hand me the AUX, I'll
get you paid Dealer plated
For the low, get you right,
spend a bag Print your tags,
print your tags, print your tags
Remote control, this device, trigger that
Switch your tags, switch
your tags, switch your tags
Running tints, pitch it
black, rig the back,
Bus a lick,. Hit the dash, really fast.
Button click: Different
tags, mission passed!
Money glitch; Did the math, split the cash
Dealer plates!
I just printed T.O.P.S. for the interstate
I just hit the auction, I'm biddin' lanes
Just hand me the AUX, I'll get you paid
Dealer plates, Dealer plates I
can vin-swap if you with the gang
If you with the cops, this
for entertainment. Just hand
me the AUX, I'll get you paid
Dealer plated